都是他出的好主意才有了这次大惨败
This entire fiasco was his big idea.
他开口最好就是说辞职
He-he opens his mouth, it better be to resign.
你可能不爱听
You may not like it,
但凡事有原则
but there are principles involved.
-什么原则  -相称性
- What principles? - Proportionality.
他们杀了我们的总统  杀了我们的特种部队
They killed our president. They killed our operatives.
和必要性
And necessity.
真正的问题是
Here's the real question:
到底要发生什么样的惨剧
what calamity has to occur before you finally admit
你才能承认应该行动起来了
it's time to do something?
是该行动  但不是这么行动
Something, yes, not this,
不是全面入侵一个已经声明
not a full-scale invasion of a nuclear power
绝不允许我们越过边界的有核国家
that has said they will not tolerate our crossing their border.
你他妈觉得最后会是什么结果
How in the fucking world do you think that'll end?